aboutprojectors.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy at About Projectors

All information and content on this website is the property of About Projectors and is protected by copyright and trademark laws of the United States and foreign countries. By using this website you agree to the following terms and conditions.

  1. This website and its contents may not be distributed or copied in any manner without prior written permission of About Projectors.
  2. About Projectors MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS WITH RESPECT TO THIS WEBSITE OR ITS CONTENTS, WHICH ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.
  3. Parts of this website may publish readers' opinions and/or comments. About Projectors does not assume responsibility or any liability for any of the opinions and/or comments.

**About Projector's Privacy Policy**

We understand the importance of your privacy as a visitor to this website. We want you to understand how information you may provide will be used.

**Information collected**

About Projectors does not collect personal information about you except for the information that you voluntarily provide. We may collect usage information of our site to analyze interest in content and to provide advertisers information on an aggregate basis. No personally identifiable information will be shared with third party advertising companies.

To use all of the services that we provide, you will be required to register and create an account on our website. We may use this information to provide targeted banners or promotions based on your interests. This personal information will not be shared and is treated confidentially. We also provide a mechanism on our website for you to opt-out of these offers or promotions.

**Community**

When using our online community functions, you will be identified by your user ID which defaults to your email address. We encourage our users to select a unique user ID to avoid providing your email address to other users and third parties. Failure to use this feature to select a unique user ID may result in other users or third parties sending you unsolicited email.

**Children's Privacy**

Our website is intended and designed for an adult audience and children under the age of 18 should not register or use our website. We will not intentionally collect personal information from minors and they may only use the site after gaining the permission of their parents or guardians.
